If you find an English three speed at a yard sale, it may have some interesting accessories on it.
They may not have been on the bike when it was originally purchased, but they were probably purchased from the bike shop later on, and put on the bike.
A wicker basket, which I showed in the previous segment is a classic add on, particularly for a woman's bike.
The men's bikes didn't really use the wicker baskets, but they look great on a woman's bike.
Lighting, as this bike has, this is after market lighting, or add on lighting, that's another popular accessory.
Another popular thing is a cyclometer.
It's a very simple mechanical device, let's you know how many miles you've gone.
There's a read out on the face of this, and there's a key which you attach to the spoke, and there's a little wheel here that gets turned every time that key passes by.
So, as this bike, the wheels spinning forward, the key goes by, it turns this lever on the cyclometer, and it slowly ticks up the miles that you've covered.
This one looks like it's got about fifteen hundred miles on it, which is a lot.
Another accessory here is the classic saddle bag.
You always see these attached to the back of a Leather Brook Saddle.
Some of these were made of leather, this is vinyl.
These are getting really hard to find, there really easy to put on, as a matter of fact, there are eyelets on the back of the saddle, for mounting them.
Basically, these straps go through the eyelets, one there, one there and then one strap around the seat post and you've got a handy saddle bag.